### Omar Boado

### Senior Programmer/ Senior Software Engineer

Innovative, forward-thinking executive offering over 4 years of success in various leadership roles in the areas of Information Technology consulting, customer support, pre-sales engineering, and global business development. Expert in strategic and tactical planning, and client relationship management (CRM).



boado.omar89@gmail.com 🔀

+63909 635 8335

San Fernando City La Union, Philippines 👂

## WORK EXPERIENCE IT Staff

Yamaha Wheeltek Corp

02/2017 - 07/2017

Maintains Computers, Printers, Internet Connection and System data/s

#### Senior HRIS Programmer

Software Engineer, Kaiser Dela Cruz Consulting Inc. - MEDSYS. San Fernando City, La Union

08/2017 - Present

A company that develops HIS (hospital Information System) and HRIS (Human Resource Information System)

#### Achievements/Tasks

- Responsible for design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of HRIS Module (Human Resource Information System) that includes
   Personnel, Biometrics, Timekeeping and Payroll Module.
- Performed production system software installations and gathering software requirements from clients(Hospitals and other bussiness establishments) and end users.
- Maintain existing Crystal Reports and rewrites/modifies according to clients format.
- Developed and Optimized Stored Procedures and Functions using T-SQL.
- Modify and customize commercial programs for internal needs.
- Can maintain, fix/troubleshoot Hardwares/Computers.
- Trained End user/s on how to use the Medsys System
- Implement HRIS (Human Resource Information System)
   Actual and Remote Impelementation, ff client: CHDG at
   La trinidad Benguet SLU Hospital in Baguio, Sacred
   Hospital in Angeles Pampanga, NKTI in Quezon City, Ace
   Hospital in Dumaguete, Rosario Hospital in Guagua
   Pampanga, VRP Hospital in Mandaluyong City, and TCHI
   in Tayabas Quezon)

#### **EDUCATION**

# Batchelor of Science in Information Technology

Saint Louis College

06/2012 - 04/2016

San Fernando City La Union

Course

Information Technology

#### Saint Louis High school - Virac Virac, Itogon Benguet

Virac Itogon Benguet

#### **SKILLS**

Programming

Communication

**Logical Thinking** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

Tagalog, Ilokano, English
Professional Working Proficiency